HÜSEYİN ŞANAL

ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONICS ENGINEER



+90 538 326 8480



huseyinnsanal@gmail.com



Pınar Mahallesi 74039 Sokak Sanrıkent 2 Sitesi B Blok K:4/D:7 Seyhan/Adana



https://www.linkedin.com/in/huseyin sanal

SKILLS

- LTspice
- Visual Studio(C++)
- CST Microwave Studio Suite
- Code Composer Studio(C)
- AutoCAD
- Microsoft Office PowerPoint
- Microsoft Office Word
- Microsoft Office Excel

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English - I graduated from the college of foreign languages with a B2 level English and I am studying 100% English.

HOBBIES

- Basketball
- Football
- · Reading Books
- Swimming
- Riding Bike
- · Playing Darts
- Playing Tennis
- New Technologies

EDUCATION

Cukurova University

Electrical Electronics Engineering 2018 - 2024

İsmail Safa Özler Anatolian High School

2013 - 2017

ABOUT ME

I am a 4th year student at Çukurova University department of Electrical and Electronics Engineering. I am a person who is open to improvement and I want to gain work experience in my field. I am a quick learner, I can easily adapt to teamwork and I have high individual productivity. I trust my communication skills, I believe that I can put extras on the expected efficiency in the studies which I participate in and the jobs I receive.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PERSONNEL

Zeplin Plastik İnşaat İç ve Dış Ticaret Limited Şirketi June 2021 - August 2022

 Mostly, I was dealing with the logistics of the company. I was responsible from storage, stock control, material and quality control, preparation for shipment and tracking. I also created price quotes and income statements in MS Excel.

PART TIME SUPPORT WORKER

Ç.Ü. Sağlık Kültür ve Spor Daire Başkanlığı Özgelirler December 2019 - April 2020

 I worked about maintenance and control of technical equipments such as microphones, smart boards and computers which are used for the lessons.

FRONT FIELD SALESPERSON

Şanal Petrol Ticaret Limited Şirketi

June 2017 - October 2017

• I was offering technical services such as refueling the vehicle, checking the battery, radiator, glass and engine water and completing it to the required level.

PROJECTS

ROCKET ENGINE TEST STAND

1.5 Adana Rocketary Team

September 2021 - January 2022

• I was the electronic member of the team and I took part in the R&D and hardware design of the electronic board which we designed with load cell to draw the thrust-time graph of the solid fuel rocket engine which we will produce. Also, I took part in the design of the wireless ignition system to provide security of people.

ACTIVITIES

October 2019 - January 2023

 Faculty of Engineering Basketball Team October 2013 - June 2018

GSİM Basketball Club

REFERENCE

Ahmet İRTEŞ

Zeplin Plastik Construction General Manager +90 532 100 2194